# LOICE OTUNDO

### +254 724 867 170

## lotundo02@gmail.com

Experienced Digital Marketer with over a year of experience in Digital Marketing. Focused and experienced in overseeing Social Media Marketing for growing organizations. Accomplished in improving lead prospecting, customer acquisition and brand awareness. Offers top skills in marketing campaign planning and project management.

### **EXPERTISE**

- Content Development
- Client Engagement

- Branding Strategies
- Graphic Design

- Creative Design
- Email Marketing

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **BUSINESS & UX/UI DESIGN INTERN**

Webtribe Limited, Nairobi

- Feb 2023 July 2023
- Developed and curated marketing campaigns and strategies for the organization.
- Assisted in marketing and advertising promotional activities.
- Contributed to the creation of mock-ups, email campaigns, and social media content.
- Supported the marketing team in daily administrative tasks.

#### FREELANCE SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER

Jan 2023 - May 2023

927 Classic Ventures Limited, Nairobi

- Planned and executed digital marketing campaigns across various channels.
- Created and optimized content for the digital marketing channels.
- Created, managed, and optimized paid advertising campaigns on platforms.
- Kept up-to-date with the latest trends, technologies, and best practices in digital marketing.

### FREELANCE SOCIAL MEDIA CORDINATOR

Sept 2021 - Jan 2023

Pamba Premier Insurance Agency, Nairobi

- Developed and curated engaging content for social media platforms
- Maintained a unified brand voice across the different social media channels
- Moderated the social media platforms to encourage conversations and respond to visitor inquiries
- Developed a social media strategy that is process-driven, consistent and measurable.

#### SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING INTERN

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021

Aldrich Property Consultants, Nairobi

- Interacted professionally and effectively through verbal and written communication.
- Participated in maintaining media database working to increase transparency and optimize operational efficiencies.
- Created strategies to help communicate content through social media networks and tools.
- Reviewed social media analytics, then developed and implemented improvements to increase effectiveness.

### **ICT - DIGITAL INTERN**

Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

Royal Media Services Limited

- Demonstrated keen attention to detail and passion for good work.
- Executed digital media strategies across online advertising, social media, and video.
- Designed and produced motion graphic content and videos for marketing internal web properties.
- Developed design briefs by gathering information and data to clarify design issues.

# LOICE OTUNDO

+254 724 867 170

# lotundo02@gmail.com

### **EDUCATION**

### United States International University - Africa, Nairobi

Aug 2016 - Sep 2020

Bachelor of Science, Information Systems and Technology GPA: 3.2

- Dean's List Fall Semester, 2017
- Member of the Kenya Red Cross Society, USIU Chapter
- Member of the Youth Alliance for Leadership & Development in Africa (YALDA), USIU Chapter

## **STUDENT PROGRAMS**

Head of Communications	2019
USIU Africa Graduation Dinner Committee	

## Communications Assistant 2018

USIU Africa Mr. & Miss Committee

### Photography and Research 2018

USIU Africa Yearbook Committee

### **ACHIEVEMENTS & CERTIFICATIONS**

Digital Freelancing	Jan 2023
---------------------	----------

African Center for Women, Information and Communications Technology

### Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Jun 2022

Google Digital Garage

Certified Network Security Specialist Apr 2022

International Cybersecurity Institute

Introduction to Cybersecurity Dec 2019

Cisco Networking Academy

IT Essentials Training Dec 2017

Cisco Networking Academy

### **REFERENCES**

Grace Gathu	Denis K. Mwabu	Chris W. Ayuoyi
H.R Manager	Senior Marketing Executive	Senior Student Affairs Officer
Webtribe Ltd.	Webtribe Ltd.	USIU Africa
+254 701 934 364	+254 792 050 166	+254 730 116 792/787
ggathu@webtribe.co.ke	dmwabu@jambopay.com	cayuoyi@usiu.ac.ke